Hey everybody. Welcome to this A2
English listening practice video. You
can use this video to practice your
listening and comprehension as I speak.
Before we start, remember to subscribe
to the channel, click on the bell, and
follow us on Instagram. You ready? So
today, I'm going to talk about road
trips. This is one of my favorite topics
because I love road trips. In case you
don't know this term, a road trip is
when you travel a long distance by car.
Let's talk about some different kinds of
road trips and how Americans usually
take road trips. So, this type of
traveling is really popular in the US.
People take road trips for several
different reasons. Maybe they don't want
to pay for a flight, maybe they want to
see some sights on the way to their
destination, or maybe they just like the
freedom of driving. I've taken many road
trips throughout the years, and I hope I
can take many more in the future. So,
the first thing you need if you want to
have a good road trip is a reliable car.
If you don't have a reliable car, you're
taking a big risk. One time, my family
and I drove from Southern California to
the state of Idaho, but around halfway
there, our car broke down. We had to
take it to a mechanic and then rent a
new car to finish the trip. It was a
complete disaster all because we didn't
have a reliable car. So, make sure
you've got a good car if you want to
take a trip like that. Another thing
that many people consider important is
having good road trip music. If you're
going to drive many hours, you probably
want to have some good music or other
entertainment. If you have this, your
road trip will probably be funner and
more exciting. Sometimes, I also listen
to podcasts while I'm driving. So, one
reason why the US is such a great place
to travel by car is that it has a very
good highway system. The whole country
is connected by highways, so you can
easily travel anywhere. And most of
these highways are pretty well
maintained. Also, the US has many
convenient places for road trippers,
such as rest stops, motels, and diners
all along the highways. I've always
loved stopping at diners in the middle
of nowhere after driving for hours and
enjoying a big hearty meal. You can
encounter some really interesting people
at these roadside diners. And as I
mentioned, we also have many rest stops
along the highways. If you get tired and
need a break, you can stop at one of
these rest stops and stretch your legs.
These stops also have restrooms, and you
can usually buy snacks from vending
machines there. One last thing that's so
cool about road trips is that they give
you a sense of freedom. It feels really
cool to be driving down the highway with
the ability to go anywhere you want.
This is one of my favorite aspects of
road trips. All right, that's all for
today. Leave a comment and tell me if
you've ever taken a road trip. And
remember to subscribe to the channel,
click on the bell, and follow us on
Instagram for more English tips and
lessons. I'll see you next time.